<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Where 2 Go</string>
    <string name="about">
		Your mission is to create a three-screen application that allows users to: search for places in Seattle, Washington using the Foursquare API; view their search results in a list or on a map; and view the individual details of each search result.\n\n

		The first screen should display an input field that allows users to search for places (for example, “coffee”, “pizza”, “Whole Foods”, etc) and, upon executing a search, should display the results in a list. Clicking an item in the list should launch a details screen. The details screen should show the place’s location on a map (for example, using Google Maps), provide details about the place, including website, and the user should be able to favorite the place on this screen.\n\n

On the main screen, when search results are visible, the screen should include a Floating Action Button. This button, when clicked, should a full-screen map with a pin marking the location of each search result. Clicking a pin should show the name of the place on the map, and clicking on the name should then open the details screen for the given place.\n\n

		Enjoy
	</string>
    <string name="google_maps_key" translatable="false" templateMergeStrategy="preserve">
        AIzaSyCKxchs2SohPaKHjPfxx_OpoR4bSIxfCEU
    </string>
    <string name="google_static_maps_key" translatable="false" templateMergeStrategy="preserve">
        AIzaSyBJ8FpHurNJQ0oyEhxY4U1HMAZ2xF_pv9w
    </string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="search_hint">What are you looking for?</string>

    <string name="search_no_results_response">Sorry, we couldn\'t find any matches for \"%s\"</string>
    <string name="venue_detail_failure">Sorry, we couldn\'t find the details of the venue you were interested in.</string>

    <string name="suggested_searches">SUGGESTED SEARCHES</string>
    <string name="no_suggested_searches">No suggestions.\n Tap \"Search\" for results</string>

    <string name="map_not_ready">Map is not ready yet</string>

    <string name="drag_melbourne">Drag Melbourne</string>
    <string name="clear_map">Clear</string>
    <string name="flat">Flat</string>
    <string name="rotation">Rotation:</string>
    <string name="reset_map">Reset</string>
    <string name="custom_info_contents">Custom info contents</string>
    <string name="custom_info_window">Custom info window</string>
    <string name="default_info_window">Default info window</string>

</resources>
